A. James Delahoussaye collection of Atchafalaya River Basin recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Interviews and Events
  - Edward Couvillier, Lena Mae Couvillier, Greg Guirard, Ray Brassieur, Larry Couvillier, and Justin Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Oxford, Louisiana, May 3, 2006
    Recorded at the residence of Edward Couvillier on Oxford Loop. Interviewees discuss Bill Sanders/Jules Chauvin shooting, shrimp and the Red River rise, Anslems and cypress, and the Little Brown Church.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (86 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR41
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (32 pages); afc2012044_sr041_transcript.doc
  - Carl Carline, Joyce Carline, Edward Couvillier, Lena Mae Couvillier, and Bob Vuillemont oral history interview conducted by James Delahoussaye at the Bayou Chene Reunion in Morgan City, Louisiana, September 16, 2006
    Recorded at Lake End Park. Interviewees discuss Mose Larson strong, a 14 foot gator, Buffalo spawn story, and “Sap” Couvillier flotation story.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (14 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR41
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (32 pages); afc2012044_sr041_transcript.doc
  - Robert Vuillemont and Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye at the Bayou Chene Reunion in Morgan City, Louisiana, September 9, 2006
    Recorded at Lake End Park, Morgan City. Interviewees discuss boats and fishing.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (65 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR42
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (36 pages); afc2012044_sr042_transcript.doc
  - Bonita Couvillier Newsome, Larry Couvillier, Justin Couvillier, and Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, November 1, 2006
    Recorded at Lena Mae Couvillier’s funeral. Interviewees tell family stories.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (14 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR43
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (5 pages); afc2012044_sr043_transcript.doc
  - Darlene Soulé, Edward Couvillier, and Liza Henry oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye near Olivier, Iberia Parish, Louisiana., January 26, 2007
    Recorded at the residence of Eliza (Liza) Louise Domingue Couvillier Henry on Crochet Road. Interviewees discuss a fire on a houseboat, McKinley's murder, orphanage, school, Lake Dauterive, medicine, courtship and marriage to Abner Couvillier, ghost stories, whisky roaches, churches, and family.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (82 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR44
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (88 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR45
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (37 pages); afc2012044_sr044_transcript.doc
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (4 pages); afc2012044_sr045_transcript.doc
  - Carl Carline, Kathy Carline, Earl Kelley oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Charenton, Louisiana, March 26, 2007
    Recorded at Tunney Carline's funeral. Interviewees discuss funerals, casket building, and stories about Tunney Carline.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (27 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR46
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (10 pages); afc2012044_sr046_transcript.doc
  - Edward Couvillier, Pamela Cameron, and James Reiter oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Oxford, St. Mary Parish, Louisiana, April 22, 2007 and July 11, 2007
    Recorded at the residence of Edward Couvillier on Oxford Loop. Interviewees discuss family, catching frogs, the Depression, fishing, Nick Burns, the future of the fishing industry, dating, grandparents, moving across the levee, sandbars, and houseboats.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (70 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR47
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (27 pages); afc2012044_sr047_transcript.doc
  - Carl Carline, Joyce Carline and Mike Soprano oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Charenton, St. Mary Parish, Louisiana, June 20, 2007
    Recorded on a boat at Lake Fausse Point, St. Mary/Iberia Parish and at the residence of Carl and Joyce Carline on Sanaren Drive. Interviewees discuss making a living in the fishing industry, ghost stories, fishing bait, pirate John Lafitte, burial mounds, and boats stuck in sandbars.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (108 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR48
    - Transcript, 1 MS Word file (30 pages); afc2012044_sr048_transcript.doc
  - Edward Couvillier, Justin Couvillier, and Larry Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Oxford, St. Mary Parish, Louisiana and at the, July 26, 2007 and
    Recorded at the residence of Edward Couvillier on Oxford Loop. Interviewees discuss the Anslem family, Couvillier family, canals, Little Pigeon Bayou, and Big Pigeon Bayou.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (42 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR49a
  - Carl Carline oral history interview conducted by James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, August 2007
    Recorded at Russell Daigle’s funeral.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio microcassette (26 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR88
  - Bayou Chene Reunion in Morgan City, Louisiana and Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, September 15, 2007
    Recorded at Lake End Park and in a vehicle. Interviewees discuss women and work.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (47 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR49b
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (94 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR50
  - Edward Couvillier, Carl Carline, and Joyce Carline oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, January 4, 2004
    Recorded at the residences of Edward Couvillier and Carl Carline.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (70 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR51
  - Carl Carline and Joyce Carline oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, January 4, 2004
    Recorded at the residence of Carl Carline.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (93 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR52
  - Elwood Stephens oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Stephensville, Louisiana, February 5, 2008
    Interviewee discusses his early days in the Stephensville area.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (35 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR53
  - Artie Hester Morgan oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, February 19, 2008
    Interviewee discusses life on Hog Island.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (92 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR54
  - Liza Henry, Hester Lange Johnson, Ed Couvillier, and Darlene Soulé oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, February 22, 2008
    Interviewees discuss early days of Liza’s life.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (94 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR55
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (47 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR56
  - Ory Mendoza oral history interview conducted by James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, March 5, 2008
    Recorded on a trip to see pullboat roads. Stan Richardson, Sue Hebert, and Harry Hebert also present.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (47 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR57
  - Steamboat Carrie B. Schwing talk by James “Fry” Himel at the Plaquemine locks, March 29, 2008
    Recorded during a slide presentation.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (64 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR58
  - Medric Martin and Stampley Luke oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Oxford, St. Mary Parish, Louisiana, January 27, 2009
    Recorded at Martin's general store on Irish Bend Road (LA 322) near location of old Oaklawn Sugar Mill.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (57 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR59
  - Edward Couvillier, Ann Couvillier, and Justin Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, February 10, 2009
    Recorded in Larry Couvillier’s hospital room.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (43 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR60
  - Ed Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, April 12, 2009
    Interviewees discuss the Metz/Anslem houseboat.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (78 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR61
  - Hester Lange Johnson oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, May 24, 2009
    Interviewee discusses her life at Hog Island.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (94 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR62pt1
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (73 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR62pt2
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (93 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR63pt1
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (71 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR62pt2
  - Howard Freeman, Carlin Lange, Ed Couvillier, Larry Couvillier, Ray Brassieur, and Lola Freeman oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, June 20, 2009
    Interviewees discuss skiff talk and old times.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (80 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR64
  - Ed Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, July 25, 2009
    Recorded during a break from boat building. Interviewees discuss law and order and shrimp bushes.
  - Ernest Burns and Ed Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, August 22, 2009
    Recorded at the residence of Ernest Burns.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (81 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR66
  - Ernest Burns and Marlene Burns oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, August 24, 2009
    Revisiting
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (82 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR67pt1
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (42 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR67pt2
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (20 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR67pt3
  - Bayou Chene Reunion, September 19, 2009
    Recorded at Lake End Park, Morgan City, the residence of Chip Metz, and in a vehicle.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (85 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR68
  - Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, October 17, 2009
    Recorded in a vehicle, at Martin's general store on Irish Bend Road (LA 322) near location of old Oaklawn Sugar Mill, and at Ryan’s while eating.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (69 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR69
  - Wallace Ackman oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, January 22, 2010
    Interviewee discusses old stories and a black man called “Fry.”
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (77 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR70
  - Keith Felder and Jules Lambert oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, March 28, 2010
    Interviewees discuss boat building.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (23 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR71
  - Bayou Chene Pilgrimage, May 22, 2010
    Recorded in put-put boats.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (84 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR72
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (7 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR73
  - EJ Daigle, Blue Daigle, Ed Couvillier, and Kevin McCaffery oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, June 10, 2010
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (84 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR74
  - Oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, July 3, 2010
    Recorded in Ory Mendoza’s shop.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (84 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR75
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (53 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR76
  - Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, August 10, 2010
    Recorded in a vehicle on the way to Wallace Ackman’s funeral.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (15 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR77
  - Butch Felterman, Jerry Marcotte, and Alberta Marcotte oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, October 16, 2010
    Interviewees discuss Father Gobeil, the French language, and seine fishing.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (48 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR78
  - Wesley Serrette oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, October 20, 2010
    Recorded at the Boure Club.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (6 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR79
  - George Lange oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, October 29, 2010
    Recorded at the residence of George Lange.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (94 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR80
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (38 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR81
  - Wilson Bailey oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, November 18, 2010
    Recorded at the residence of Wilson Bailey.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (97 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR82
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (48 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR83
  - Gillian Daigle oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, 1980s
    Recorded by Gillian Daigle at the residences of the interviewees. Copies included in this collection by A. James Delahoussaye.
    - Sound recording, 1 .WAV file (27 minutes); afc2012044_sr084a.wav
    - Sound recording, 1 .WAV file (24 minutes); afc2012044_sr085a.wav
    - Sound recording, 1 .WAV file (49 minutes); afc2012044_sr086a.wav
    - Sound recording, 1 .WAV file (45 minutes); afc2012044_sr087a.wav
  - Annual Meeting of Antique Putt Putt Boat Owners, March 28, 2011
    Recorded at J.B. Castagnos’ camp on Belle River. Interviewees discuss engines stories, old boats and the swamp.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (90 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR89
  - Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, April 29, 2011
    General conversations about the old days.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (90 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR90
  - Edward Couvillier and Kevin Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, February 29, 2011
    Recorded while cleaning catfish.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (90 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR91
  - Delma Meaux and Nel Meaux oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Delcambre, Louisiana, November 3, 2011
    Interviewee was the last school teacher at Bayou Chene.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (90 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR92
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (60 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR93
  - Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, November 5, 2011
    Recorded while riding in vehicle. Interviewees discuss oil field experience, finances in the Basin, fishing by Burns family, net dipping, tarring, and girls at Bayou Chene.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (90 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR94
  - Edward Couvillier oral history interview conducted by A. James Delahoussaye in Louisiana, November 29, 2011
    Recorded at Emily Kelley Carline’s funeral. Interviewees discuss early fishing days, outdoor toilets, pulling contests with putt putt boats, floating moss, and storage using barges with a closed cabin.
    - Sound recording, 1 audio cassette (90 minutes); AFC 2012/044: SR95
- Series III: Photographs
  Six hundred and thirty-five digital photographs (copies of original family print photographs) collected by Darlene Soulé from 11 families in the Atchafalaya River Basin, Louisiana, arranged by ID number.
  - Photographs from Bailey Albert and Agnes Sauce Bailey
    - Agnes and Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph001.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph002.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph003.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph004.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph005.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph006.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph007.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr. with Hoopnet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph008.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr. and Lynwood "Peanut" Couvillier with Albert "Putt" Couvillier's boat, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph009.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph010.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph011.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Eula Daigle, and Joseph Mire, 1927, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph012.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier's house, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph013.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr. and Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph014.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., Carol Ann Bailey, and Amanda Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph015.jpg
    - Albert "Putt" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph016.jpg
    - Albert "Putt" Couvillier, Milton Bailey, and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph017.jpg
    - Albert "Putt" Couvillier, Dorothy Couvillier, Lynwood "Peanut" Couvillier, Kim Couvillier, and Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph018.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey and Preston Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph019.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey and Rosalie Mayon Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph020.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey, Albert Bailey Jr., Lola Mae Millet, and Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph021.jpg
    - Amanda and Joseph Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph022.jpg
    - Amanda White, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph023.jpg
    - Barbara Sauce (Robert and Gertrude's daughter), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph024.jpg
    - Barbara Sauce (Robert and Gertrude's daughter), 1951, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph025.jpg
    - Barbara Sauce (Robert and Gertrude's daughter), 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph026.jpg
    - Berinda Ann Millet, Alberta Bailey, Justin Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph027.jpg
    - Berinda Ann Millet, EJ Daigle and Leroy Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph028.jpg
    - Bill and Odelia Daigle Orgeron, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph029.jpg
    - Byron Daigle and Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph030.jpg
    - Carlin Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph031.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, Albert Bailey, and Lola Mae Millet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph032.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph033.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph034.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph035.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1962, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph036.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph037.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph038.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph039.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph040.jpg
    - Carol Bailey and Amanda White, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph041.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, Albert Bailey, Jr., Edward Couvillier, and Justin Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph042.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, Albert Bailey, Jr., and Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph043.jpg
    - Cleo J. "Neg" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph044.jpg
    - Cleo J. "Neg" Sauce and son Joseph Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph045.jpg
    - Donna Marcotte at age 7, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph046.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey and Bonita Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph047.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1956-1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph048.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey's graduation, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph049.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey's graduation, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph050.jpg
    - Edward and Lena Mae Couvillier's first house, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph051.jpg
    - Edward and Lena Mae Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph052.jpg
    - EJ Daigle, 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph053.jpg
    - EJ Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph054.jpg
    - EJ Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph055.jpg
    - EJ Daigle, Albert Bailey, and Leroy Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph056.jpg
    - Elmira "Nene" Daigle Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph057.jpg
    - Emma Mayon (sister of Rosalie), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph058.jpg
    - Ernestine Daigle Bailey Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph059.jpg
    - Felix Blaise and Rosalie Mayon Sauce's houseboat, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph060.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte, Jr., Kim Couvillier, Gwen, Kevin, and Bonita, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph061.jpg
    - Felix Blaise and Rosalie Mayon Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph062.jpg
    - Felix Blaise and Rosalie Mayon Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph063.jpg
    - Erma (Emma), Claiborne, Fannie Mae, Lydia B., Ivy Paul, and Rosal, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph064.jpg
    - Gloria Ann Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph065.jpg
    - Gloria Ann Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph066.jpg
    - Gloria Ann Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph067.jpg
    - Harry Lange and Alberta Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph068.jpg
    - Hester Lange and bridesmaids, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph069.jpg
    - Hester Lange and bridesmaids, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph070.jpg
    - Hipolite Terrence Mayon (b.1834), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph071.jpg
    - Hipolite Terrence Mayon (b.1834), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph072.jpg
    - Homer Daigle (Albert Bailey Sr.'s stepdad), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph073.jpg
    - Homer Daigle (Albert Bailey Sr.'s stepdad), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph074.jpg
    - Honk Sauce (Jack's brother), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph075.jpg
    - Honk Sauce (Jack's brother), 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph076.jpg
    - Ira Lee Lange, 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph077.jpg
    - Issac Daigle, Irene Daigle, and Bonita Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph078.jpg
    - Issac Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph079.jpg
    - Issac Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph080.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph081.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph082.jpg
    - Jessie "Lil Neggie" Daigle, Jr., 1947, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph083.jpg
    - Kent Bailey and Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph084.jpg
    - Kent Bailey and Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph085.jpg
    - Kent Douglas Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph086.jpg
    - Kent Douglas Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph087.jpg
    - Kent Douglas Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph088.jpg
    - Kent Douglas Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph089.jpg
    - Kent Douglas Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph090.jpg
    - Kevin Couvillier, Gwen Couvillier, Edward Couvillier, and Bonita Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph091.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier and Harold Kelly's wedding, February 4, 1978, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph092.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph093.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph094.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph095.jpg
    - Larry Couvillier, Kevin Couvillier, Gwen Couvillier, Bonita Couvillier, and Justin Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph096.jpg
    - Laurence Sauce and Ophelia Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph097.jpg
    - Lena Mae Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph098.jpg
    - Lena Mae Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph099.jpg
    - Leona "Poona" Sauce Ruff, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph100.jpg
    - Leroy Daigle, 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph101.jpg
    - Leroy Daigle, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph102.jpg
    - Lily Hester Lange, 1951, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph103.jpg
    - Lily Hester Lange, 1970, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph104.jpg
    - Lily Hester Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph105.jpg
    - Lily Hester Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph106.jpg
    - Linda Darlene Bailey, 1963, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph107.jpg
    - Linda Darlene Bailey, 1966, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph108.jpg
    - Linda Darlene Bailey, 1968, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph109.jpg
    - Linda Darlene Bailey, 1969, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph110.jpg
    - Linda Darlene Bailey, 1972, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph111.jpg
    - Linda Faye Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph112.jpg
    - Lisa Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph113.jpg
    - Lola Mae Millet and Amanda White, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph114.jpg
    - Lola Mae Millet, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph115.jpg